bookfresh.com 2013-11-03

# Privacy Policy : Appointment Software for Your Business - BookFresh

## Privacy and Security Policy BookFresh (hereinafter "Company")

We respect your privacy.  We have established this Privacy and Security Policy so that you may better understand the information we collect and the manner in which we collect, use and disclose the information collected so that you may make informed decisions when using the Companys web-based services (including the Company hosted website(s)) (collectively "Company Service(s)").

The Company Services are used by both businesses (incorporated or otherwise) ("Businesses") who register for the Company Services and by the customers and/or potential customers of such Businesses ("Consumers").  We collect information from the Businesses and Consumers and we also collect information in connection with the operation, maintenance and usage of the Company Services.

By using or accessing the Company Service(s), you are accepting and agreeing to the practices described in this Privacy and Security Policy.

Information You Post

In connection with the Company Services, Businesses and/or Consumers may choose to upload, publish or otherwise display, or share with others (collectively, "post") certain material, including contact information, photos, personal information, messages, notes, text, and/or any other content (collectively the "User Content") on or through the Company Services.   You agree that you are posting the User Content at your own risk and Company and its partners or agents are not responsible for the use, confidentiality, disclosure or security of such User Content; This Privacy and Security Policy is not applicable to User Content you publically post. 

The Types of Information We Collect

Registration Information for Businesses:  When a Business registers to use the Company Services, in the registration process, Company collects certain registration information from the representative of the Business, including the Business name, a user name and password to be used by the Business representative, and other the contact information for the Business representative, such as email, address and telephone number, etc. (collectively "Registration Information").

Billing Information:  When a Business purchases fee-based services/products from Company, Company will also collect billing information from the Business representative, such as credit card number(s) ("Billing Information").

Other Information Collected from Businesses and Consumers in Connection with Company Service Offerings:

a. Information about the Business Operations:  In connection with the Company Services, Company may also collect certain information about the Business and its operations, including, the geographic location of the Business, the services and/or products offered by the Business, a general description of the Business operations (including hours of operation), pricing, policies, names of staff members/contractors, contact information for staff members/contractors (including but not limited to email addresses, phone numbers, names of such personnel), photographs of business and/or staff members/contractors, etc.  (collectively "Business Information").  

b. Consumer Information:  In connection with the Company Services, Company may also collect certain information (including personally identifiable information) about the Consumers of the Businesses.  For example, Businesses may input and/or upload certain information about their Consumers and the Consumers of the Business may input and/or upload such information about themselves (collectively "Consumer Information").

c. Aggregate Site Usage Information:  Company also collects aggregate information from the users of the Company Services  regarding the users systems and their usage of the Company Services (including but not limited to, information derived from the web browsers of the users of the Company Services including information derived from "cookies" or similar technology, Internet Protocol addresses collected from server logs, traffic and volume statistical data, frequency of visits, type and time of transactions, statistical data, browser type, operating system, activity on site, links to external sites, clicks on advertisements, volume statistical information, etc.) (collectively "Aggregate Site Usage Information").

How and When We Use Information Collected

Company (and/or its business partners or contractors) may use any and/or all of the information collected or provided by Businesses and/or Consumers for the following general purposes: (a) to provide, maintain, administer, and update the Company Services; (b) to analyze and evaluate usage of the Company Services; (c) to support the users of the Company Services, including to correct any errors or failures of the Company Services; (d) to customize any marketing, advertising, and/or other content presented to users of the Company Services; (e)  to fulfill requests for Company Services and/or products; (f) to improve Company Services; (g) to conduct research, and/or (h) to provide anonymous reporting and/or data for internal and external clients.

Company (and/or its business partners or contractors) also uses the information collected in the following more specific ways:

Registration Information may be used by Company (and/or its business partners or contractors) to authenticate the representatives of the Business, to contact and communicate with the Business and its representatives, to provide information regarding service updates, to provide service updates and/or other useful information to the Business and/or its representative.  

Billing Information is used by Company (and/or its business partners or contractors) to charge for services and/or products purchased.

Business Information is deemed public information (including any personally identifiable information provided as contact information) and may be published on the internet, including to third party web sites in order to advertize or promote the Business products/services.

Aggregate Site Usage Information is used by Company (and/or its business partners or contractors) to diagnose technical problems, to administer the Company Services, for product development and testing, for backup/recovery purposes, to improve the quality and types of Company Services delivered, to analyze the usage and customize the content and/or advertising appropriately, and/or to market/validate services and products offered.  

Company (and/or its business partners or contractors) may use "cookies" or similar technologies to identify user traffic patterns and user technology, to collect usage information and aggregate demographic information, to assist Company in delivering the Company Services, to improve Companys offerings and/or services, to authenticate users, to identify users, to provide a more positive and/or personalized user experience and/or to facilitate access to user accounts, etc.  Company (and/or its business partners or contractors) may use third party advertising companies to serve ads and these third parties may send cookies or similar technologies to your computer.  Such technologies may be used to tailor the content of information delivered to you. Please understand that Blocking cookies and/or similar technologies may interfere with your use of some of the Company Services.

Company (and/or its business partners or contractors) may also use the Business and/or Consumer contact information to communicate with the Business and Consumers.    For example, if you are the Consumer, Company (and/or its business partners or contractors) may send you emails containing information you requested from the relevant Business. If you are the Business, Company (and/or its business partners or contractors) may send you emails containing information you have requested from the Consumers.  Generally, you may configure your personal account settings to set the frequency of emails or opt-out of certain promotional emails; See the section on Communications below.

How and When We Share Information Collected.

Sharing Required to Provide Services: We will share the information we collected from you as necessary and contemplated by the Company Services in order to provide/administer and/or facilitate Company Services.  For example, we would share a Consumers name/contact information with the Business they were contacting.  By using Company Services you agree that you are consenting to disclosure of your personally identifiable information but only to the extent disclosure is necessary to provide or facilitate providing the Company Services you are requesting. 

Agents/Contractors: We may contract with third parties to perform certain tasks on our behalf.  We might share certain information we collect with such third parties in order to perform those tasks; examples include sending email, analyzing information, and providing user services. Unless we otherwise inform you, Company's agents/contractors will not be granted any rights to use any personally identifiable information we share with them beyond what is necessary to perform such services.

Company Business Partners: In certain instances, Company Services are offered jointly with our business partners. For example, Company may partner with third parties to offer a private labeled hosted service or a co-branded service. You can easily recognize when a business partner of ours is associated with a particular service offering/opportunity/transaction, and we will share user information that is related to such service offering/opportunity/transaction with that affiliated business partner.  All such information will be delivered to our business partner, subject to the partners agreement to comply with the terms of this Privacy and Security Policy.

Aggregate Non-Indentifying Information:  We may provide aggregate non-identifying information (specifically including Aggregate Site Usage Information) to third parties in order to market our products/services and to demonstrate the value we deliver. 

Third party advertisers: Third party advertisers that may advertise on the Company hosted site(s) generally have no access to any personally identifiable information unless you choose to share it with them. However, third party advertisers may have access to anonymous usage data in order to target contextually relevant advertisements. Advertisements may be served directly to users by third party advertisers. In such cases, the third party advertiser will automatically receive your IP address. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Company does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. 

Sale or Merger of the Business or Portions of the Business; Business Transfers:  If at some point Company sells all or a portion of its assets, or merges with another entity, or if Company goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, the Company data (including user information collected) may be transferred or acquired by a third party in an asset sale or transfer. After such a transaction, the third party that becomes the custodian of the information/data purchased would have the right to continue using the information/data as set forth in this policy. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer may continue to use your information as set forth in this policy.

Compliance with Laws; Protection of Company and Others: Company may release information collected (including personally identifiable information) if it believes in good faith that the release/disclosure is necessary to comply with laws or regulations, supeonas, or the requests of law enforcement or other government authorities or that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce/apply Companys Terms of Service or other agreements, or that disclosure is required in order to protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, its employees, our users, or other third parties. This includes, without limitation, exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

Disclosures With Your Consent: Except as set forth herein, users will be notified when their personally identifiable information may be shared with third parties, and will be given the option to prevent the sharing of this information.  

Relationship and Disclosures between the Consumers and Businesses:

To the extent you are the Consumer and you provide information to the Business via Company Services or otherwise (including but not limited to any personally identifiable information you provide to the Business), Company is not responsible for the Business use or disclosure of such information.  For example if you provide your email address or other personally identifiable information to a Business via the Company Services or otherwise, the Business may use that information and contact you with promotional or other information or disclose that information to others.  You understand and agree that Company is in no way responsible for such use or disclosures of such information.  

Similarly, to the extent you are the Business and provide information to the Customers via Company Services or otherwise (including personally identifiable information you make available to the Consumers via the Company Services or otherwise), Company is not responsible for the Consumers use or disclosure of such information.

All information exchanged between Business and Consumers via the Company Services or otherwise, is exchanged at your sole risk and Company is not responsible to control the actions of the Business or Consumers.

Third Party Sites

The Company site is collaborative, and may contain links to multiple third party sites on the Internet, including many that have different privacy and security policies and practices. Company makes no representations or warranties about the policies and practices of sites that are linked to the Company sites or its users. We urge you to consult the policies available on those sites to further understand your rights and their practices. 

Security

Company has implemented processes designed to protect the information its collects and stores. Registered users are assigned a unique user name and password which are required to access their account. It is the user's responsibility to protect the security of their user name and password. Company has employed firewalls and other advanced security technologies which we belive to be appropriate in an effort to prevent unauthorized interference or access from outside intruders.  However, Company cannot guarantee the security of its systems or any information stored or maintained on its systems as no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.  Also, Company cannot control the actions of others. Unauthorized entry or use or disclosures, hardware or software failures, and other factors may compromise the security of the information Company collects and stores.  Company is not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures used in connection with Company Services. 

Accessing, Correcting and Revising Registration and Contact Information

If you need to update or change your information, you may so by editing your user record/account information. To update your record/account information, log on to the service and select the available user account management pages.

If you choose to cancel your account, please be aware that we may retain residual/historical information in our data bases for audit, legal or other purposes. 

Communications; Email Opt-Out

As part of our Services, you agree that Company may contact you and send you communications as the Company deems reasonably necessary. Company may also, from time-to-time, send you certain promotional emails/communications. To stop receiving promotional emails/communications you may opt out, see our Email Opt-Out Page.

Compliance with Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

As a business service, Company does not target its offerings toward, and does not knowingly collect any personal information from users under 13 years of age.

Changes to the Privacy and Security Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy and Security Policy and will provide notification of any material change. Any changes shall be effective after you receive notice of the change prospectively.  If you do not agree with the changes, you can terminate your account and/or stop using the Company Services and such change will therefore not apply to you.  

You may contact us with any questions pertaining to this policy at privacy@Bookfresh.com.

Last Updated: 11/18/2012
